CONTACT



6369376676



 $evaitheesh wari {\tt O1@gmail.com}$



https://www.linkedin.com/in/vaitheeshwari-e-191465208



Villupuram, Tamilnadu.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Salesforce Certified Associate
- Salesforce Certified Al Associate
- Salesforce Certified Al Specialist
- Salesforce Certified
 Administrator
- Salesforce Certified App builder
- Salesforce Certified Advanced
 Administrator
- Salesforce Certified Platform
 Developer I
- Salesforce Certified Sales
 Cloud Consultatnt
- Pega Certified System Architect
- Pega Certified Senior System
 Architect

LANGUAGE

- Tamil
- English
- Telugu

VAITHEESHWARI E

DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Motivated, team-oriented and highly responsible Computer science engineer with significant experience in developing solutions and analysing the business requirements. Experienced in configuring / building new and enhanced functionality in the Salesforce platform using declarative / programmatic solutions. Having hands-on experience working in LWC and Apex. Ability to have clear and strong communication skills and collaborate with others. Strong analytical and problem-solving person that continuously working towards personal and organization growth.

WORK EXPERIENCE

TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER Oct 2023 - Present

SALES CLOUD

- Worked on various developing topics such as Integrating external system
 with salesforce org predominantly using REST. I have implemented the
 Integration for many customers both using REST and SOAP. Majorly used
 postman as a third party tool and have experience using workbench. Have
 hands-on experience in using various flows such as username password
 flow, Web-server, JWT and more for integration.
- Have hands-on in implementing SSO in production org with identity provider for securely logging into salesforce with IDP credential. Gained enormous knowledge on SP initiated and IDP initiated flow for SSO.
- I have worked on implementing Triggers, apex classes and test classes for customers based on certain business use cases they had, in following the best practices and code coverage of 100 percentage for test classes.
- I have hands on in implementing batch classes for inserting and updating records in org. Wrote triggers only using context variables and implemented handler classes to handle rest of the functionalities and called them using triggers.
- Involved in implementing Lightning Web Components for various use cases such as displaying the customer history in a data table using wire to fetch data from apex methods. Have implemented various features such as toast messages, infinity loading, refresh apex, etc in customer orgs.
- Interacted with multiple customer across the world to understand their business scenarios and issues and help them to resolve them, implement new use cases they might have. Worked on urgent cases and issues and resolved their issues with no escalations.

- I have expertise in analyzing the logs thoroughly to point out root cause of an issue and find the right solution to resolve it quickly.
- Having vast hands on experience in implementing flows as per the best practices such as handling it with bulk records, not using DML operations inside loop and many more.
- Worked on various business scenarios and thought out of the box to achieve irregular use cases such using formula fields, callouts, different variable data types and more.
- Involved in implementing Async apex(Future, Batch, Queueable, Schedulable) considering the business cases and figuring out optimal solution and implementing the same.
- Have created packages both 1GB and 2GB. Worked on components to bundle together into a package that can help other customers. I have worked on plenty of cases where I have solved in troubleshooting the packaging issues.

SYSTEM SOFTWARE ASSOCIATE PROGRAMMER

Aug 2022 - July 2023 Serendebyte Inc. - TTEC

SALESFORCE DEVELOPER

- Experienced in Apex classes, Batch Apex, Schedulable Apex, Validation Rules, SOQL, Triggers, Web Services and Callouts.
- Hands-on experience in Lightning flows and Process Builders.
- Developed and deployed 20+ LWC components.
- Developed 35+ Apex Classes and Test Classes with code coverage of 85% and more with best practices.
- Gone through Salesforce corporate training for around 3 months.
- Hands-on experience in Salesforce CRM Analytics studio.
- Design applications with Unit test, Integration test and deployment with better user interface.

Service Cloud

- Developed Service Cloud application for a client project.
- Worked on Lightning Service Console, Web to case, Case management and flows.
- Having a significant Hands on experience in creating custom reports and dashboards to provide a 360-degree view of customers by presenting relevant data.
- Used Einstein Prediction and Next Best Actions to make better outcome of data.
- Follow agile methodologies and Devops software development practices.

Marketing Cloud

- Worked on an Internal Project in Marketing Cloud.
- Hands-on experience in using different components of marketing cloud as such Journey builder, Content builder, Data Extensions, Email Templates and Path optimizer.
- Actively participate/lead walk-through/demos and reviews with the team(as needed).
- Integration of Marketing Cloud with Sales Cloud to pull the salesforce data in Marketing Cloud.

INTERN

May 2022 - Aug 2022

Serendebyte Inc. - TTEC

PEGA

- Worked on Case Type configuration, Decision components, Reports for Mobile Connection application.
- Experienced in UI Customization, Flow, Flow Actions, Data Pages, Processes and Job Scheduler.
- Integrated Instamojo with pega for payment process.
- I am a self determined person and enthusiastic to work on different Use case scenarios.

EDUCATION

2018 - 2022	BACHELOR OF ENGINEERING Chennai Institute of Technology, Chennai.	Percentage - 88%
2017 - 2018	HSE Government Girls Higher Secondary School, Villupuram.	GPA 8.9
2015 - 2016	SSLC Government Girls Higher Secondary School, Villupuram.	Percentage - 96.4%

SKILLS

Salesforce	Apex	VS Code
SOQL	LWC	Integration
Pega	HTML	Tableau
Javascript	JAVA	С
CRM Analytics	Postman	SSO

- 116,450+ Trailheads Points
- 210+ Badges with Trailhead Double star ranger
- 8X Salesforce Certified
- Solved over 100+ problems in different coding websites in Apex.